Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory10 Mss.B.B61.inventory10
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents P
  - Prokosch, Eduard (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Weigand, Herman J., 1936 Mar. 3
  - Proposed General Anti-Fascist Organization of ed. Latin America (Box 72)
    - 1938 Dec. 31, 3p
  - Proskauer, J.M. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 18; 1p
  - Prosser, C.K.K. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept 28; 1p
  - Protat, A. [or Ch.] (Box 72)
    - To Boas, Feb. 11 1920; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept.11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 17; 2p
    - Cosigned, W.L. Ney, 1932 Dec. 16
    - To Benedict, R.F., 1927 May 30; 2p
    - To Benedict, R.F., 1927 July 15; 1p
  - Protat, E.M. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept.18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 12; 2p
  - Protat Freres (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 20 and Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 4
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Aug. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 21 and Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 21; 1p
  - Provost, Geo. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 23; 2p
  - Pruette, L. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 8; 2p
  - Pruitt, O.J. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 14; 1p
  - Przibram, Hans (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Pruneda, Alfonso (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1911 July 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Aug. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - see FB to Engerrand, 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 June 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 24; 10p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 June 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 July 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 June 19
    - To Boas, 1914 July 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Tozer, A.M., 1914 Jan. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 9
  - Psychological Register (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1931 July 31; 4p
  - Psychologische Institut of Berlin (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Puchallen (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 4
  - Puckett, N.N. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Stechert, G.E., enc. with Stechert, G.E., 1924 Nov. 18; 2p
  - Puckette, C.M. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 12; 1p
  - Puerto Rico (Box 72)
    see Nolla, J.A.B.
    see Howe, Marshall A.
  - Pugliesi, A. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 16; 1p
  - Pupin, M.I. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Stephen P. Duggan, 1920 May 3; 1p
  - Purin, C.M. (Box 72)
    - To Baginsky, P., 1934 June 13; 1p
  - Purpus, C.A. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 10; 1p
  - Putnam, A.J. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Putnam, C. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
  - Putnam, E.K. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 19; 1p
  - Putnam, E.O. (Box 72)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 7
  - Putnam, F.W. (Box 72)
    - From Boas, 1893 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1894 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1894 July 20
    - From Boas, 1894 July 25
    - From Boas, 1894 Aug. 28
    - From Boas, 1895 July 6
    - From Boas, 1895 Sept. 6
    - From Boas, 1895 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1895 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1895 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1896 May 6
    - From Boas, 1896 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1896 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 31; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 6; 4p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 May 4
    - From Boas, 1909 May 28
    - From Boas, 1909 June 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 June 12
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 3
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 5; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10 and Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1891 May 26
    - To Boas, 1891 May 31
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1894 May 18 and Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1894 May 1
    - To Boas, 1894 May 10
    - To Boas, 1894 May 14
    - To Boas, 1894 June 2
    - To Boas, 1894 June 13
    - To Boas, 1894 June 25
    - To Boas, 1894 July 2
    - To Boas, 1894 July 4
    - To Boas, 1894 July 16
    - To Boas, 1894 July 22
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1895 June 8
    - To Boas, 1895 June 19
    - To Boas, 1895 July 2
    - To Boas, 1895 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1896 May 8
    - To Boas, 1896 May 9
    - To Boas, 1896 May 24
    - To Boas, 1896 June 20
    - To Boas, 1896 July 2
    - To Boas, 1896 July 6
    - To Boas, 1896 July 6
    - To Boas, 1896 July 23
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1897 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1897 July 28
    - To Boas, 1897 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1897 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1898 June 6
    - To Boas, 1898 June 8
    - To Boas, 1898 June 12
    - & FB to Jesup, M.K., 1898 June 15
    - To Boas, 1898 June 21
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1899 May 14
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1900 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1903 July 22
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 May 29
    - To Boas, 1905 June 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 July 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 May 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 29 and Dec. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 5
    - To Boas, 1909 June 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 May 21
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 May 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Crawford, Saml. A., 1894 Mar. 7
    - To Hewett, E.L., 1906 Feb. 8
    - To Jesup, M.K., 1898 Apr. 11; 4p
    - To Lowell, Augustus, 1897 Mar. 20
    - To Lowell, Augustus, 1898 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Pritchett, H.S., 1906 Aug. 20
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 28
  - Putnam, G.H.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 17
  - Putnam, G.P. Sons (Amer. Anthropologist) (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 18, Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1899 May 3
    - From Boas, 1899 May 4, May 9
    - From Boas, 1899 May 25
    - From Boas, 1899 June 3, June 1
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 8
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1899 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1899 Sep. 8
    - From Boas, 1899 Sep. 13
    - From Boas, 1899 Sep. 16
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1900 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 13
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1900 May 5
    - From Boas, 1900 May 8
    - From Boas, 1900 May 11
    - From Boas, 1900 May 16
    - From Boas, 1900 June 3
    - From Boas, 1900 June 5
    - From Boas, 1900 July 30
    - From Boas, 1900 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1900 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 11
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1901 May 27
    - From Boas, 1901 Sep. 3
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 21 and 9
    - From Boas, 1902 May 1
    - From Boas, 1902 June 17 and May 5
    - From Boas, 1902 Sep. 4
    - From Boas, 1902 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1902 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1902 Sep. 19
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 5; 1p
      - publication agreement, 1899 Jan. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1899 Jan. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 May 2, 7, May 9
    - To Boas, 1899 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 May 26
    - To Boas, 1899 June 2
    - To Boas, 1899 June 5
    - To Boas, 1899 June 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1899 July 3
    - To Boas, 1899 July 12
    - To Boas, 1899 July 12
    - To Boas, 1899 July 31
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1899 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 12
    - To Boas, 1899 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1899 Oct. 24; 5p
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 20, Mar. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 26; 6p
    - To Boas, 1900 May 7
    - To Boas, 1900 May 9
    - To Boas, 1900 May 17
    - To Boas, 1900 Sep. 17; 7p
    - To Boas, 1900 Sep. 19
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1901 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1901 May 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1901 June 4; 10p
    - To Boas, 1901 June 12
    - To Boas, 1901 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1901 Sep.
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 31; 13p
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1902 May 5
    - To Boas, 1902 May 7
    - To Boas, 1902 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1902 Sep. 13; 7p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 5
    - From Andrews, H.A., 1902 Sep. 19
    - To Hodge, F.W., 1899 Feb. 7
    - To Hodge, F.W., 1899 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Hodge, F.W., 1902 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Jesup with FB, 1898 June 15
  - Putnam, Haven (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 5
  - Putnam, Harbert, Librarian, L.C. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb 17
    - From Boas, 1917 May 22
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 May 22
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 8
    - From Laufer, B., 1917 May 26
  - Putnam, J.B. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 11; 2p
  - Putnam, Ruth (Box 73)
    - To Boas?, 1911 July 30; 3p
  - Putnam, W.C. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Sep. 27
  - Putnam, W.M. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents Q
  - Quackenbos, G. Payn (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 10
  - Quain, Buell (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 28
    - From Ottenberg, Reuben, 1934 Nov. 12
  - Quebec, Dir., Ecole d'Agricul., St. Anne de la PocatiC(re (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 19
  - Quesada, E. (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15
  - Quidde, Ludwig (Box 73)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct.
  - Quintero, G.F. (Box 73)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 June 30
    - To Boas, 1917 July 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 29; 2p
  - Quiring, J., 1925 Jan. 14 (Box 73)
    - 1925 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 20